[
  {
    "question": "What were Maya pyramids made of?",
    "answer": "Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a military building?",
    "answer": "Scout Camp"
  },
  {
    "question": "The prehistoric humans known as 'homo floresiensis' are also commonly referred to as?",
    "answer": "Hobbit"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the largest animal on the planet?",
    "answer": "Blue whale"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Phoenician civilization originated in which part of the world?",
    "answer": "The Eastern Mediterranean"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Achilles refused to fight, Patroclus puts on Achilles armor, fights the Trojans, and dies. Who is Patroclus killed by?",
    "answer": "Hector"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these characters is from 'Twenty Thousand leagues Under the seas'?",
    "answer": "Captain Nemo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these city themes looks like a vehicle?",
    "answer": "On the wings of sailcloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who designed the djoser, the first ancient pyramid featuring a stepped design?",
    "answer": "Imhotep"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not an objective of Greek mythology?",
    "answer": "Provide a path for salvation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following organs is part of the human respiratory system?",
    "answer": "Lungs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is not in Europe?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "During a solar eclipse, the celestial object that comes between the Sun and the earth is:",
    "answer": "The Moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who founded the 'Spanish Armada'?",
    "answer": "Philip II"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is julius Caeser's nickname in Rise of Kingdoms?",
    "answer": "The Uncrowned Emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What two major works are attributed to Homer?",
    "answer": "The Odyssey and The Iliad"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a natural resource?",
    "answer": "Clothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "A crater on the far side of the Moon is named after a Chinese official who was (supposedly) the first person to travel into space. What was his name?",
    "answer": "Wan Hu"
  },
  {
    "question": "A decrease in which of the following metrics might indicate increasing nearness to a state of vacuum?",
    "answer": "Air pressure"
  },
  {
    "question": "A human fingernail is made of which material?",
    "answer": "Alpha-keratin"
  },
  {
    "question": "A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm. Which of Isaac Asimov's Three Laws of Robotics is this?",
    "answer": "First law"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Greek mythology, which two gods transformed into the 'fish' in the symbol of Pisces?",
    "answer": "Aphrodite and Eros"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Maya chronology, the Late Late Preclassic Period falls within:",
    "answer": "1 BCE to 159 CE"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the tale of the She-wolf in Roman mythology, what came of the twins she nurtured, Romulus and Remus?",
    "answer": "Romulus became the founder and first King of Rome"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to World Athletics, which of these is NOT an official international discus weight?",
    "answer": "1.25kg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Acquiring Commander William I unlocks which of these achievements?",
    "answer": "Path of Glory"
  },
  {
    "question": "Advantages of Johannes Gutenberg's printing press include all of the following except what?",
    "answer": "Increase in church power"
  },
  {
    "question": "After a Venus Flytrap catches an insect, how does it digest and absorb the prey?",
    "answer": "The inner flaps of the leaves secrete a digestive fluid"
  },
  {
    "question": "After its foundation in the 6th century BCE, which institution of the Roman Republic served as a consultative parliament?",
    "answer": "The Senate"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the Lost Kingdom opens, what item do you have to spend to teleport to and from the Lost Kingdom?",
    "answer": "Random Teleport"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the students at the Lyceum of Wisdom finish their lessons, what building in your city do they return to?",
    "answer": "Academy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Afterglow is caused by:",
    "answer": "Light scattering in air"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alliance help can NOT speed up which of the following activities?",
    "answer": "Troop training"
  },
  {
    "question": "Amethyst is valued for its brilliant violet hue. What mineral is it a variety of?",
    "answer": "Quartz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apart from 'Number of Scouts' and 'Power', which of the following Scout Camp parameters can also be upgraded?",
    "answer": "Scout March Speed and Exploration Range"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apart from 'Times You Can Be Helped' and 'Power', which of the following Alliance Center parameters can also be upgraded?",
    "answer": "Reinforcement Troop Capacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2018 World Cup, how many times has Shakira performed at the World Cup closing ceremony?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2018 World Cup, how many World Cups has Brazil won?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2018 World Cup, what is the United State's best ever World Cup result?",
    "answer": "Third place"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2018 World Cup, which player holds the record for most goals scored in a single World Cup match with five goals?",
    "answer": "Oleg Salenko"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2018 World Cup, who holds the record for most goals scored in the World Cup?",
    "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2018 World Cup, who holds the World Cup record for fastest goal scored at 11 seconds?",
    "answer": "Hakan Şükür"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2022 World Cup, how many countries have won the World Cup?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 21st World Cup, who is the only player to have scored a hat-trick in 2 different World Cups?",
    "answer": "Gabriel Batistuta"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ashoka the Great was the King of which Ancient Indian kingdom?",
    "answer": "Maurya"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assuming the absence of any other special buffs, which of these commanders has the highest march speed?",
    "answer": "Belisarius"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what level does the Trading Posts transport tax rate become 10%?",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what VIP level can you purchase a VIP Special chest that contains enough Hannibal Barca sculptures to awaken him?",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "At which VIP level do you permanently unlock a second building queue?",
    "answer": "Lvl. 6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bhutan is also known as the Land of the Thunder Dragon. What is its capital and largest city?",
    "answer": "Thimphu"
  },
  {
    "question": "Big Ben is located in which of the following countries?",
    "answer": "United Kingdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "Black Forest Cake is a famous European dessert. In which country is the Black Forest from which it takes its name?",
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bossa nova is a popular genre of music originating from which country?",
    "answer": "Brazil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Broccoli is rich in which vitamin?",
    "answer": "Vitamin C"
  },
  {
    "question": "By what other name are Ceroli Chieftains Ak & Hok also known by?",
    "answer": "The Astral Twins"
  },
  {
    "question": "By what other name is October also known under Japan's old calendar?",
    "answer": "Kannazuki"
  },
  {
    "question": "By what other name is the Ceroli Chieftain Wafura also known?",
    "answer": "Wolfshadow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cactus spines are actually a modified form of which other part of the plant?",
    "answer": "Leaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Champagne is a region in which country?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "Charles Macintosh crafted a very early version of a raincoat from which material?",
    "answer": "Rubber"
  },
  {
    "question": "China's 'crosstalk' sketch comedy format originates in three places: Tianqiao in Beijing, the Quanye Bazaar in Tianjin, and where in Nanjing?",
    "answer": "Fuzimiao"
  },
  {
    "question": "Combat Tactics is an important Military Technology - what effect does it have?",
    "answer": "Increases Attack of all units"
  },
  {
    "question": "Commander Björn Ironside's 'Viking Lord' skill benefits which of the following unit types?",
    "answer": "Infantry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Darwin's last book primarily discussed which species' influence on soil?",
    "answer": "Earthworms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Diego Velázquez, the painter of the realist work Portrait of Pope Innocent X, was from which country?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "During China's Warring States Period, which state defeated the other six and built the unified Chinese empire?",
    "answer": "Qin"
  },
  {
    "question": "During nuclear fusion, which of the following elements produces less energy than it absorbs?",
    "answer": "Iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Renaissance, why was Florence significant?",
    "answer": "Birthplace and symbol of the Renaissance"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Second Punic War, in which battle did a vastly outnumbered Hannibal defeat a Roman army?",
    "answer": "The Battle of Cannae"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Trojan War, which Greek warrior killed Hector?",
    "answer": "Achilles"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Upper and Lower Egypt period, what color was the crown of the pharaoh of Upper Egypt?",
    "answer": "White"
  },
  {
    "question": "During which emperor's reign was the Roman Colosseum completed?",
    "answer": "Titus"
  },
  {
    "question": "During which season are nights relatively short and days relatively long?",
    "answer": "Summer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Edward VIII became King of England in January 1936. Later in the same year, in which month did he give up the throne?",
    "answer": "December"
  },
  {
    "question": "Egypt's economy was primarily based on what?",
    "answer": "Agriculture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Egyptians made paper from which material?",
    "answer": "Papyrus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Elbe Day was the meeting of which two armies during World War II?",
    "answer": "USA, USSR"
  },
  {
    "question": "Equipment with special talent bonuses will have their attributes enhanced by what percentage when equipped to a commander with the corresponding talent?",
    "answer": "30%"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feijoada is considered a national dish of which country?",
    "answer": "Brazil"
  },
  {
    "question": "First created in Ancient Greece, to which profession does the Hippocratic Oath apply?",
    "answer": "Doctors"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fish and chips has its earliest origins in which country?",
    "answer": "England"
  },
  {
    "question": "Focaccia is a type of pizza-like bread. Which country (and its cooking culture) created the focaccia?",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Foie gras is a very nutrient-rich food. Which country produces the most foie gras?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "For every 1 unit you train in your city, how many expedition units do you get in Expedition mode?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "For how many francs did Charles V ransom Bertrand du Guesclin during the conflict over Brittany?",
    "answer": "100000"
  },
  {
    "question": "For which disease did Edward Jenner, known as the father of immunology, develop a vaccine?",
    "answer": "Smallpox"
  },
  {
    "question": "France and Germany were both once part of what feudal Kingdom?",
    "answer": "Francia"
  },
  {
    "question": "French National Day is on July 14 in order to coincide with which historical event?",
    "answer": "Storming of the Bastille"
  },
  {
    "question": "From the 17th to 19th centuries, the Kingdom of Prussia was mostly in which modern country?",
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "From the 8th to the 11th century CE, what did Europeans frequently call the Scandinavian invaders who frequently ravaged their lands?",
    "answer": "Vikings"
  },
  {
    "question": "Galileo's Leaning Tower of Pisa experiment overturned a theory of which Ancient Greek scientist?",
    "answer": "Aristotle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Global warming will NOT lead to:",
    "answer": "A drop in sea levels"
  },
  {
    "question": "Governors cannot earn Activity Points through which of the following?",
    "answer": "Expeditions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Halley's Comet can be observed from Earth every",
    "answer": "75-76 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "Held in 1929, how long did the first Academy Awards ('Oscars') ceremony take?",
    "answer": "15 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hieroglyphs were part of which country's formal writing system?",
    "answer": "Ancient Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Homer's epic 'The Iliad' focuses on events happening during which war or battle?",
    "answer": "The Trojan War"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you get Alliance Technology Credits?",
    "answer": "By donating to research Alliance Technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you obtain the Friend of the Kingdom achievement?",
    "answer": "Visit 100 tribal villages"
  },
  {
    "question": "How high in the Sunset Canyon daily ranking do you need to place before you can receive the Golden Key Daily Rewards?",
    "answer": "In the top 5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long did the Hundred Years War between England and France last?",
    "answer": "116 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long does the 'Basic Army Expansion' boost last?",
    "answer": "4h"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long does the rune dropped by defeating the Guardians remain on the map?",
    "answer": "8 hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many 'Golden Kingdom Equipment Troves' are contained within the Golden Chest earned from stage 16 of the 'Golden Kingdom' event?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many arrows are stuck in the shield of commander Lohar?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many beasts can you expect to see fighting alongside Lvl 20 barbarian troops in Rise of Kingdoms",
    "answer": "1 bear and 2 wolves"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many bones does an adult human normally have?",
    "answer": "206"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many bowmen are shown practising in the Archery Range when training composite bowmen?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many cards in total are shown in the Mysterious Merchant's hands?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many daily Activity Points do you need in 'Lucerne Scrolls' to claim the Daily Gift clue reward?",
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many days are in a leap year?",
    "answer": "366 days"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many dispatches do you need to complete at the State Forum to open a Dispatch Commendation?",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Easter eggs are featured in the Easter Egg Avatar Frame?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many emeralds are featured on the clothing of commander Matilda of Flanders?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many flags are featured in front of the Alliance Center for the French civilization?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many gears are shown on the icon for the Economic Technology 'Engineering'?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals does a player need to score to earn a hat-trick?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Golden Keys are awarded to the top finishing Governor in each season of Sunset Canyon?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many hurricanes were recorded around the Pacific Ocean in the year 1977?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many individual credits can be earned from selling normal equipment blueprints through the Alliance Shop's reclaim feature?",
    "answer": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many individual quests does an Expedition involve?",
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many items of the same quality should I equip to complete 'Ready For Battle'?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Key Points are required to unlock the Treasure of Blue Crystal in Alliance Gifts?",
    "answer": "3000000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many keys are included in the Alliance Gift received for the destruction of a Lvl 5 Barbarian Fort?",
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many keys are included in the Wooden Chest Alliance Gift?",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many keys does a typical modern piano have?",
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Legendary Commander Sculptures are awarded to the top finisher by total rankings in the 'The Mightiest Governor' event?",
    "answer": "180"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many letters are used in today's version of English?",
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Medals of the Conqueror are needed to purchase a Legendary Commander Sculpture in the Medal Store in Expedition mode?",
    "answer": "1500"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many minutes' worth total of speedups can be obtained from purchasing the '7-Day Speedup Supply' in addition to the immediate 1,050 Gem reward?",
    "answer": "3,150 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Normal Iron Ore do you need to make an Advanced Iron Ore?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many officers (excluding the alliance leader) can an alliance have?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Olympic gold medals did African-American athlete Jesse Owens win in 1936?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many patrolling soldiers roam a governor's walls?",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many phases are there in The Mightiest Governor event?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many players are there in the board game Go?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points are earned per 1 point of upgraded Power within the 'Stage 4: Power Upgrade' segment of 'The Mightiest Governor' event?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points are gained per Lvl 3 unit severely wounded/killed in the 'Stage 5: Enemy Elimination' segment of the 'Mightiest Governor' event?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many polar bears feature on the Heart of the North Avatar Frame?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many refreshes are available per visit to the Mysterious Merchant?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many reward chests are awarded for reaching 60 daily activity points?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many roses feature on the Rose Petals Avatar Frame?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Scouts can the Scout Camp hold at once?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sections are featured in the Kingdom Newspaper outside of special calendar events?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many separate khanates or empires had the Mongol Empire fractured into by the time of Kublai's death in 1294?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many small tents can you see in a Lvl 3 Barbarian Fort?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many stars are featured on the banner displayed behind the commander Minamoto no Yoshitsune?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many students sit in on the lectures held by the scholars of the Lyceum of Wisdom?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams competed in the 2022 World Cup?",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many teams took part in the first World Cup?",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many tents are shown on the icon for the Military Technology 'Encampment'?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many tiles does a City Hall occupy within your city?",
    "answer": "9x9"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times can you receive alliance help if your Alliance Center is level 14?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times can you receive alliance help if your alliance center is level 25?",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times has North Korea qualified for the World Cup?",
    "answer": "Two times"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times is the character '1' used when you write from number 1 to number 99?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many troops are recommended for destroying a Lvl 3 Barbarian Fort?",
    "answer": "480,000 Lvl 3 units"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many troops can governors send with a level 17 City Hall or above?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many VIP points can you buy with 200 gems?",
    "answer": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Watchtowers are included in a Lvl 25 city?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many wheels are there on a battering ram?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Women's World Cups has Megan Rapinoe won?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many World Cup titles has Italy won?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many World Cup titles has Pelé won?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years are there between each Winter Olympic Games?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much capacity does a Lvl 15 Hospital provide (excluding boosts)?",
    "answer": "29000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much does the 12-Hour Enhanced Attack item increase your troops' Attack by?",
    "answer": "5%"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much experience does a commander earn from a Lvl 7 Tome of Knowledge?",
    "answer": "50000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much gold does a single issue of the Kingdom Newspaper cost?",
    "answer": "1000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much reinforcement troop capacity does a city receive at Alliance Center Lvl 20?",
    "answer": "575000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much stone will a Lvl 17 Quarry produce every hour (excluding boosts)?",
    "answer": "2775"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much total daily contribution is required to place in the daily alliance contribution rankings?",
    "answer": "10000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much will an Enhanced Attack (Advanced) item increase your attack?",
    "answer": "10%"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much will an Enhanced Gathering item increase your gathering speed?",
    "answer": "50%"
  },
  {
    "question": "How often does the World Cup take place?",
    "answer": "Every 4 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "How often is the FIFA World Cup held?",
    "answer": "Every 4 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "How was the Gutenberg Bible put into mass production?",
    "answer": "Movable type printing press"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a man with type AB blood and a woman with type B blood have a baby, which of the following statements would be incorrect?",
    "answer": "It could have type O blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Iguazu Falls lies on the border of which two countries?",
    "answer": "Brazil and Argentina"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Republic', what does Plato identify as the 'highest form'?",
    "answer": "Form of the Good"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1582, Oda Nobunaga was betrayed and ambushed by his general Akechi Mitsuhide. Where did this occur?",
    "answer": "Honnō-ji Temple in Kyoto"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1970, an Apollo mission attempted to land on the moon. Due to a technical issue, it only managed to orbit around the moon and return to Earth. What was the name of the mission?",
    "answer": "Apollo 13"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1970, which goalkeeper made the 'save of the century' against Pelé?",
    "answer": "Gordon Banks"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2002, FIFA published a fan-selected World Cup Dream Team. Who was the goalkeeper?",
    "answer": "Lev Yashin"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2010, at age 71, Otto Rehhagel became the oldest person to manage a World Cup team. Which team did he manage?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2018, which country set the record for being the least-populated country to ever reach the World Cup?",
    "answer": "Iceland"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2026, the US, Mexico, and Canada will co-host the World Cup. How many teams will be participating?",
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ancient Egypt, which of the following was NOT a privilege of being a 'Scribe'?",
    "answer": "Exempt from paying medical expenses if sick"
  },
  {
    "question": "In ancient Greece, the Delian League was led by which city-state?",
    "answer": "Athens"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ancient Greece, which philosopher liked to discuss ideas on a street which then got the nickname 'Peripatetic School?",
    "answer": "Aristotle"
  },
  {
    "question": "In ancient Greece, who was the high priestess of the Temple of Apollo at Delphi?",
    "answer": "The Pythia"
  },
  {
    "question": "In ancient Greek mythology, who was Hermes' father?",
    "answer": "Zeus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In ancient Greek mythology, who was the wife of Hades, the king of the underworld?",
    "answer": "Persephone"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ark of Osiris, how many teleports does the first alliance to occupy an obelisk earn?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ark of Osiris, what effect does the Desert Storm skill have on enemy troops?",
    "answer": "Deals skill damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ark of Osiris, what is the requirement for an alliance to participate in the Golden Battlefield?",
    "answer": "Ranked top 20 for alliance power in their kingdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ark of Osiris, where are you supposed to take the Ark?",
    "answer": "A non-enemy building"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Ark of Osiris, which Speedup can you use?",
    "answer": "Healing Speedup"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the nickname of K'inich Janaab' Pakal in RoK?",
    "answer": "Sun of the Eternal Glory"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these equipment is of legendary quality?",
    "answer": "The Milky Way"
  },
  {
    "question": "In China's Han Dynasty, who opened the Silk Road on the orders of Emperor Wu?",
    "answer": "Zhang Qian"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chinese mythology, what kind of creature is Jingwei?",
    "answer": "A bird"
  },
  {
    "question": "In French novelist Stendhal's The Red and the Black, what is the name of the ambitious protagonist?",
    "answer": "Julien"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Golden Kingdom, how many passes do you need to clear to get a Golden Chest?",
    "answer": "4 Passes"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, to whom did Paris, the Prince of Troy, give a golden apple inscribed with, 'To the most beautiful goddess'?",
    "answer": "Aphrodite"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, what is the Goddess Eos known as?",
    "answer": "Goddess of the Dawn"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, what is the relationship between Zeus and Hermes?",
    "answer": "Father and son"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, what was Achilles' only weak point?",
    "answer": "His heels"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, what was the name of Hades' 3-headed dog which guarded the gates of the Underworld?",
    "answer": "Cerberus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, which hero quested for the Golden Fleece?",
    "answer": "Jason"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, which hero rode the flying horse Pegasus?",
    "answer": "Bellerophon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, who is the hero known for stealing fire from the gods and giving it to humankind?",
    "answer": "Prometheus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, who ran the chariot of the sun off its path, setting the earth aflame?",
    "answer": "Phaethon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In her in-game dialogue, who does Cleopatra VII mention was assassinated by his own senators?",
    "answer": "Julius Caesar"
  },
  {
    "question": "In his in-game dialogue, who does Lohar say is the 'cruelest man' he's ever met?",
    "answer": "High Chieftain Gavar"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Homer's epic 'The Iliad', which of the following goddesses was NOT part of the competition for the Golden Apple?",
    "answer": "Artemis"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Japan, 'torii' gates are usually placed at the entrance of what buildings?",
    "answer": "Shrines"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Japan, which fruit is known as the 'fruit of immortality'?",
    "answer": "Tachibana"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Maya mythology, how many levels are there in the heavens and the underworld combined?",
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Morse code, what is the length in dots between two words?",
    "answer": "7 dots"
  },
  {
    "question": "In most cases, which kind of lion has a mane?",
    "answer": "Adult male"
  },
  {
    "question": "In mythology, who was hit by the lead arrow of Eros?",
    "answer": "Daphne"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Norse mythology, the ravens Huginn and Muninn were the companions of which god?",
    "answer": "Odin"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Norse mythology, what variety of trees was the World Tree?",
    "answer": "Ash"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Norse mythology, who does the hammer Mjolnir belong to?",
    "answer": "Thor"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Norse mythology, who wielded the weapon Gungnir?",
    "answer": "Odin"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, how many soldiers stand in front of the gates of your city?",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, the Cataphract is which civilization's special unit?",
    "answer": "Byzantium"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, the Hwarang is which civilization's special unit?",
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, the Janissary is which civilization's special unit?",
    "answer": "Ottoman Empire"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, the Throwing Axeman is which civilization's special unit?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, there is a road paved with golden bricks that can be purchased for 100 Gems. What is it called?",
    "answer": "King's Road"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, what do you have to do to complete the quest 'Sword of the King'?",
    "answer": "Recruit 200 infantry units"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, what is the maximum number of Goldmines a player can build?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, what is the nickname of the commander Constance?",
    "answer": "Queen of Sicily"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which building can you use to view your kingdom's history?",
    "answer": "Monument"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which commander can dispel enemy Attack buffs?",
    "answer": "Amanitore"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which commander has the nickname 'Queen of Sicily'?",
    "answer": "Constance"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which commander has the skill 'Beauty and Wisdom'?",
    "answer": "Cleopatra VII"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which commander has the title 'Beloved of Thoth'?",
    "answer": "Thutmose III"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which commander is nicknamed 'Queen of Silla'?",
    "answer": "Seondeok"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which Kingdom Chronicles chapter requires all fog in your kingdom to be fully explored?",
    "answer": "Long Peace"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of Sun Tzu's skills is enhanced by his expertise skill?",
    "answer": "Art of War"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of the following armaments can be used with the arch formation?",
    "answer": "Emblem of the North"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of the following characters does Sun Tzu mention in his Trust dialogue?",
    "answer": "Mulan"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of the following decorations has to be purchased with Gems?",
    "answer": "Vase"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of the following is considered a Boost item?",
    "answer": "Peace Shield"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of the following is NOT one of Mulan's skills?",
    "answer": "Clever Heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "In RoK, which of these commanders is NOT good at leading archer units?",
    "answer": "Saladin"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Roman mythology, which animal is the goddess Minerva often associated with?",
    "answer": "Owl"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Russian history, what nickname was the first Tzar given for their tyranny?",
    "answer": "Ivan the Terrible"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Shakespeare's Macbeth, the titular character murders King Duncan of Scotland. What is the name of Duncan's eldest son?",
    "answer": "Malcolm"
  },
  {
    "question": "In soccer, which position is allowed to touch the ball with their hands while it is in their team's penalty area?",
    "answer": "Goalkeeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Sunset Canyon, how many troops can you deploy at a time?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 'Batman' series by DC Comics, which iteration of Robin died as a result of a reader vote?",
    "answer": "Jason Todd (Red Hood)"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 'Gather Resources' stage of the Mightiest Governor event, how many points do you get for gathering 1 gem?",
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 16th-17th centuries, which disease did the famous bird-masked 'plague doctors' treat?",
    "answer": "Bubonic plague"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 1966 World Cup, England manager Alf Ramsey began using a unique formation that led England to the World Cup title. What was notable about this formation?",
    "answer": "No wingers"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2006 World Cup, Switzerland did not concede a single goal in regular play. Who was their goalkeeper?",
    "answer": "Pascal Zuberbühler"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2006 World Cup, who was the only English player to score during penalties in England's quarter-final match against Portugal?",
    "answer": "Owen Hargreaves"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2010 World Cup Final between Spain and the Netherlands, which Spanish player scored the game-winning goal?",
    "answer": "Andrés Iniesta"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2010 World Cup, which goalkeeper saved two penalty kicks during regular play?",
    "answer": "Brad Friedel"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2014 World Cup Final between Germany and Argentina, which German player scored the game-winning goal?",
    "answer": "Mario Götze"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2014 World Cup held in Brazil, how many cities held match venues?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2014 World Cup held in Brazil, how many Confederation of African Football teams qualified for the tournament?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2014 World Cup, which of the following teams was not in the same group as the eventual champions Germany?",
    "answer": "England"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2018 World Cup, Thibaut Courtois won the Golden Glove award for best goalkeeper. What country is he from?",
    "answer": "Belgium"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2018 World Cup, what other countries were in England's Group G?",
    "answer": "Belgium, Panama, Tunisia"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2018 World Cup, which of the following teams was not in the same group as the eventual champions France?",
    "answer": "Germany"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2022 World Cup, how many teams made it through the group stage to the knockout stage?",
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2022 World Cup, which two teams stayed in university accommodations?",
    "answer": "Argentina, Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2022 World Cup, who faced the host country Qatar in the opening match?",
    "answer": "Ecuador"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2022 World Cup, who was the first team to be eliminated?",
    "answer": "Qatar"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 49 BCE Roman civil war, who was Julius Caesar's primary opponent?",
    "answer": "Gnaeus Pompeius Magnus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Book of Exodus, who leads the Jewish people to the Promised Land?",
    "answer": "Moses"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the COMMANDER VIEW page, what buff do commanders acting as a 'Bloodfist Guard' get?",
    "answer": "Troop Health +1%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the COMMANDER VIEW page, what buff do commanders acting as a 'Drillmaster' get?",
    "answer": "Troop Attack +1%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the COMMANDER VIEW page, what buff do commanders acting as a 'Iron Guard' get?",
    "answer": "Troop Health +1%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the COMMANDER VIEW page, what buff do commanders acting as a 'Ranger' get?",
    "answer": "None of these answers are correct"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the COMMANDER VIEW page, what buff do commanders acting as a 'Tax Officer' get?",
    "answer": "Gathering Speed +5%"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the competition for the Golden Boot, if two players have scored the same number of goals, how is the winner determined?",
    "answer": "Assists"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Desire of Victory event, how can players gain rewards?",
    "answer": "Training troops"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Emerald Tablet, Hermes Trismegistus claims to hold 'three parts of the wisdom of the whole world'. Which of these is NOT one of the three parts?",
    "answer": "Transfiguration"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Grimms' fairy tale 'Town Musicians of Bremen', a group of animals travels to Bremen together to become musicians. Which of the following animals is NOT in the group?",
    "answer": "Pig"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Lohar's Trial event, how can players obtain Bone Necklaces?",
    "answer": "Defeating ordinary Barbarians"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Peerless Scholar event, how many answers do you need to get correct in the Preliminary to quality for the Midterm?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the simplified Maslow''s hierarchy of needs, which need is at the top of the pyramid?",
    "answer": "Self-actualization"
  },
  {
    "question": "In total, how many goals were scored at the 2018 World Cup?",
    "answer": "169"
  },
  {
    "question": "In total, how many matches were played at the 2018 World Cup?",
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what century was a settlement established near the mouth of the Amstel, which would eventually become the city of Amsterdam?",
    "answer": "12th century"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what city did Henri I de Bourbon, Prince of Condé, pass away?",
    "answer": "Saint-Jean-d'Angély"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what climate does basil, known in Europe as the 'King of Herbs', largely grow?",
    "answer": "Tropical areas"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what country did the 'Battle of Marengo' take place?",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what era of Chinese history did the 'Battle of Fei River' take place where a small number of soldiers conquered a vastly superior force?",
    "answer": "The Eastern Jin Dynasty"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Einstein publish his four Annus Mirabilis ('Miracle Papers')?",
    "answer": "1905"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Maradona score his 'Hand of God' goal?",
    "answer": "1986"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Mark Zuckerberg create Facebook?",
    "answer": "2004"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Qatar host the World Cup?",
    "answer": "2022"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the current World Cup trophy come into use?",
    "answer": "1974"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did the Late Show with David Letterman first premiere?",
    "answer": "1993"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was FIFA founded?",
    "answer": "1904"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first Women's World Cup held?",
    "answer": "1991"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first World Cup held?",
    "answer": "1930"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which century did the classic English dessert sticky toffee pudding originate?",
    "answer": "The mid-20th century"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city in the United States has McDonald's established a Hamburger University?",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city is Denmark's statue of The Little Mermaid located?",
    "answer": "Copenhagen"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city is FIFA headquartered?",
    "answer": "Zurich"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city is the Obelisk of Thutmose III currently held?",
    "answer": "Istanbul"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city was the world's first international soccer match held?",
    "answer": "Glasgow"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which commander's background picture can you see a chicken?",
    "answer": "Queen Tamar of Georgia"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which commander's background picture can you see a sakura tree?",
    "answer": "Minamoto no Yoshitsune"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country did assam tea, known for its rich aromas, originate?",
    "answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country did the 'Olé, Olé, Olé' chant originate?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country did the Carlist Wars take place during the 19th century?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country is the Lighthouse of Alexandria, one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, located?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country is the mysterious Stonehenge located?",
    "answer": "United Kingdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was air conditioning invented?",
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was Botticelli, painter of The Birth of Venus, born?",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was Carlsberg Group, a leading brewer, founded in 1847?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was mozzarella cheese first produced, broadly associated with Italian cooking and pizzas?",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was the 20th World Cup held?",
    "answer": "Brazil"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was the electric rice cooker invented?",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was the famed revolutionary and military strategist Simón Bolívar born?",
    "answer": "Venezuela"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was the microscope invented?",
    "answer": "The Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country was the Somme, the most infamous battlefield in World War I, located?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country were instant noodles first invented?",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country were the Wars of the Roses fought?",
    "answer": "England"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which English palace did the 'Star Chamber' sit?",
    "answer": "Palace of Westminster"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which English stadium was the 1966 World Cup Final held?",
    "answer": "Wembley Stadium"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which era of French history was the Arc de Triomphe built?",
    "answer": "Napoleonic era"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which era was the very first pyramid of ancient Egypt constructed?",
    "answer": "The Third Dynasty of Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which gallery is the Mona Lisa currently held?",
    "answer": "The Louvre"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which lake is Olkhon Island located?",
    "answer": "Lake Baikal"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which of these campaigns did Thutmose III take part?",
    "answer": "The Battle of Megiddo"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which of these works does Sherlock Holmes make his first appearance?",
    "answer": "A Study in Scarlet"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region did the popular health food hummus originate?",
    "answer": "Middle East"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region in Italy is the Cathedrawl of Santa Maria del Fiore located?",
    "answer": "Tuscany"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region was the empire of Srivijaya located?",
    "answer": "Southeast Asia"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which theater was Beethoven's Symphony No. 5 in C Minor debuted in 1808?",
    "answer": "The Theater an der Wien"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which two years was the World Cup suspended due to World War II?",
    "answer": "1942 & 1946"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which UK city were The Beatles founded in 1960?",
    "answer": "Liverpool"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which World Cup did England captain Harry Kane score 6 goals, earning him the Golden Boot award?",
    "answer": "2018 Russia World Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which World Cup did Spain win its first World Cup?",
    "answer": "2010 South Africa World Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year did Alexander Fleming discover penicillin?",
    "answer": "1928"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year did every World Cup start having a mascot?",
    "answer": "1966"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year did Richard the Lionheart and Saladin sign a truce?",
    "answer": "1192"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the Battle of Guandu?",
    "answer": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the first edition of 'The Diary of Anne Frank' published?",
    "answer": "1947"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the first Wimbledon Tennis Championship held?",
    "answer": "1877"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the Napoleonic Code established?",
    "answer": "1804"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the Soviet Union formally established?",
    "answer": "1922"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the Tianwen-1 Mars probe launched?",
    "answer": "2020"
  },
  {
    "question": "In whose workshop did Leonardo da Vinci apprentice?",
    "answer": "Andrea del Verrocchio"
  },
  {
    "question": "Insufficient intake of which element may cause the thyromegaly?",
    "answer": "Iodine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Into what kind of deity was Imhotep deified following his death?",
    "answer": "A god of medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Into what shape does commander Yi Seong-Gye's fan-shaped active skill transform after gaining Expertise?",
    "answer": "A circle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Japanese ivy grows upward on walls and trees in order to capture energy from which source?",
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "Johannes Vermeer, the painter of Girl with a Pearl Earring, was from which country?",
    "answer": "The Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "Keira once defied the world's expectations about her in a glorious battle. Where did this battle take place?",
    "answer": "Sunset Canyon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Know thyself was a widely-known aphorism of which country?",
    "answer": "Ancient Greece"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lactose intolerance is caused by a shortage of what?",
    "answer": "Lactase"
  },
  {
    "question": "Last of the Romans is an epithet used to describe someone with a classical Roman way of thinking. Who could NOT exemplify that?",
    "answer": "Attila"
  },
  {
    "question": "Legendary commander of the Joseon Dynasty, Yi Sun-sin, sacrificed his life in which famous battle?",
    "answer": "Battle of Myeongnyang"
  },
  {
    "question": "Li Xin, the ancestor of the 'Flying General' Li Guang, was a general of which state during the Warring States period of Chinese history?",
    "answer": "Qin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Machu Picchu is a notable relic of which civilization?",
    "answer": "The Incas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Man of Peace is the nickname of which commander?",
    "answer": "Imhotep"
  },
  {
    "question": "Messi has used 6 different jersey numbers in his career. What are those 6 numbers?",
    "answer": "10, 14, 15, 18, 19, 30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Methods of mitigating desertification do NOT include:",
    "answer": "Overexploitation of groundwater"
  },
  {
    "question": "Military strategist Belisarius served as a personal bodyguard to which emperor in his youth?",
    "answer": "Justinianus I"
  },
  {
    "question": "Miroslav Klose holds the record for most goals scored in the World Cup. How many goals has he scored?",
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Murasaki is a character in which of the following works?",
    "answer": "Tale of Genji"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mutations are important because they bring about what?",
    "answer": "Genetic variation needed for a population to evolve"
  },
  {
    "question": "Northern Humanists like Erasmus were most commonly known for what?",
    "answer": "Interest in religious and social reform"
  },
  {
    "question": "Noted Danish archaeologist Christian Jürgensen Thomsen proposed the 'three ages' system for categorizing ancient history. Which is the first stage?",
    "answer": "Stone Age"
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the 12 Chinese Zodiac animals, which comes first?",
    "answer": "Rat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the below commanders, which is best suited to lead troops AGAINST archer enemies?",
    "answer": "Cao Cao"
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the below commanders, which is best suited to lead troops AGAINST cavalry enemies?",
    "answer": "Hermann"
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the below commanders, which is best suited to lead troops when gathering resources?",
    "answer": "Seondeok"
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following, which is most likely to have directly led to the Bronze Age?",
    "answer": "Bronze is harder and more durable than other metals available at the time"
  },
  {
    "question": "On its tragic maiden voyage, what was the Titanic's intended destination?",
    "answer": "New York"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which animal was the 2018 Russia World Cup's mascot based on?",
    "answer": "Wolf"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which continent did the serval first live?",
    "answer": "Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which continent is Benin located?",
    "answer": "Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which continent is the human race generally thought to have originated?",
    "answer": "Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which ingredient was the 1986 Mexico World Cup's mascot based on?",
    "answer": "Pepper"
  },
  {
    "question": "One 'day' on the planet Venus is approximately equal to how many earth days?",
    "answer": "243 days"
  },
  {
    "question": "One hundred forty thousand all disarmed! Among these was there not a single man? Which Tang-dynasty poet wrote this couplet?",
    "answer": "Madame Huarui"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the benefits of canned food is its long shelf life. Where were the first canned herrings made?",
    "answer": "Northern Europe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pandas have 5 clawed toes on as well as a sixth digit. What do pandas use their sixth digit for?",
    "answer": "To hold bamboo while eating"
  },
  {
    "question": "Passport Pages are used when immigrating to other Kingdoms. What does the number of Passport Pages used depend on?",
    "answer": "Governor's Individual Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "Peppers have been farmed for millennia. Which continent can we trace their origins back to?",
    "answer": "The Americas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Puncture Wounds is the skill of which character in Ceroli Crisis?",
    "answer": "Astrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Qatar follows Arabia Standard Time. How would that be notated using UTC?",
    "answer": "UTC+3:00"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen Guinevere fell in love with which Knight of the Round Table according to Arthurian legend?",
    "answer": "Lancelot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Queen Victoria of England was part of which royal house?",
    "answer": "The House of Hanover"
  },
  {
    "question": "Raphael is best known for his creation of which of the following?",
    "answer": "School of Athens"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ru ware is one of the most famous types of Chinese pottery, known for its delicate pale blue glaze. Which dynasty did it originate from?",
    "answer": "Song"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sandro Botticelli's painting 'Venus and Mars' is famed for its vivid colors and beautiful figures. In which gallery is this painting now housed?",
    "answer": "The National Gallery in London"
  },
  {
    "question": "Santa Claus travels on a sleigh pulled by what animal?",
    "answer": "Reindeer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Screenwriter Marguerite Duras is known for writing the film 'Hiroshima mon amour'. Where was she born?",
    "answer": "Vietnam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Seondeok was Queen of Silla (part of modern-day Korea). What was her birth name?",
    "answer": "Kim Deokman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shanghai's Jin Mao Tower has how many floors?",
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since its founding in 1863, how many times has the International Committee of the Red Cross won the Nobel Peace Prize?",
    "answer": "3"
  }
]
